Guide to the Re-Imagining Collection, 1993-2016 RL.11352
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Re-Imagining Collection
1993-2016
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.11352
3 Linear Feet Two boxes of audio cassettes, one box of papers.
5.7 Gigabytes MP3 audio files, electronic text files
Re-Imagining is an ecumenical, radical, Christian movement focused on creating ways of understanding Womanist, Feminist, Mujerista, and Asian Feminist theologies, and opening spaces for dialogue with the church, diverse religious communities, and the world. Eighty-two audio files comprise an oral history project by Sherry E. Jordon with 73 participants in the Re-Imagining conferences, including the first gathering in 1993, Re-Imagining: A Global Theological Conference By Women: For Men and Women. Additionally, 127 mp3 files and 79 audiocassettes comprising Re-Imagining conference sessions and rituals from gatherings in 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1998, and 2000, as well as three linear feet of papers documenting Jordon's work with Re-Imagining.
Arrangement
Oral histories arranged alphabetically, conference materials arranged chronologically.
Historical note
Re-Imagining: A Global Theological Conference By Women: For Men and Women, was organized by Mary Ann Lundy (Director of the Presbyterian Church USA's Women's Unit), Sally Hill, and other mainline protestant leaders in the United States, to be part of the World Council of Churches' Ecumenical Decade: Churches in Solidarity with Women 1988–1998. The 2,200 attendees, met at the Minneapolis Convention Center on November 4 to 7, 1993, participating in presentations and rituals re-imagining male-centric images and language of traditional Christianity.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Re-Imagining Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2016.
Collection Overview
Re-Imagining is an ecumenical, radical, Christian movement focused on creating ways of understanding Womanist, Feminist, Mujerista, and Asian Feminist theologies, and opening spaces for dialogue with the church, diverse religious communities, and the world. Eighty-two audio files comprise an oral history project by Sherry E. Jordon with 72 participants in the Re-Imagining conferences, including the first gathering in 1993, Re-Imagining: A Global Theological Conference By Women: For Men and Women. Additionally, 127 mp3 files and 79 audiocassettes comprising Re-Imagining conference sessions and rituals from gatherings in 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1998, and 2000, as well as papers documenting Jordon's work with Re-Imagining. Interviewees and speakers include Martha O. Adams, Jann Aldredge-Clanton, Gail Allan, Elizabeth Andrew, Diana Butler Bass, Mary Farrell Bednarowski, Elizabeth Bettenhausen, Nadean Bishop, Kathy Black, Donna Blackstock, Steven Blons, Robert Brinkley, Rita Nakashima Brock, John M. Buchanan, Nancy Chinn, Faye Christensen, Hyun Kyung Chung, Susan Cole, J. Ann Craig, Susan Halcomb Craig, Kathy Deacon-Weber, Sister Holy Spirit DeSouza, Heather Murray Elkins, Sara M. Evans, Marylee Fithian, Mary Gates, Marchelle Hallman, Susan Hames, Robin Henry, Maren Hinderlie, José Hobday, Mary E. Hunt, Pamela Carter Joern, Sally Howell Johnson, Katie Johnson, Barbara Anne Keely, Betty Kersting, Judith Allen Kim, Annie Wu King, Rebecca Lynn Kiser, Mary Kuhns, Pui-lan Kwok, Barbara Lund, Barbara K. Lundblad, Mary Ann Weese Lundy, Katherine Austin Mahle, Eily Marlow, Joan M. Martin, Mary Kaye Medinger, Joyce Ann Mercer, Virginia R. Mollenkott, Melanie S. Morrison, Susan Morrison, Mary Clark Moschella, Vivian Jenkins Nelsen, Randy Nelson, Christie Neuger, John Niles, Manley Olson, Ofelia Ortega, Doris Pagelkopf, Rebecca Todd Peters, Virginia Pharr, Joy Mincey Powell, Mary Preus, Anne Primavesi, Bernice Johnson Reagon, Jo Ringgenberg, Mary Kay Sauter, Jeanyne B. Slettom, Jerie Smith, Joyce D. Sohl, Hilda Spann, Allison Stokes, John Strausz-Clement, Judith Strausz-Clement, Sue Swanson, Hal Taussig, Margaret Thomas, Rebecca Tollefson, Carmen Valenzuela, Johanna W.H. Van Wijk-Bos, Emily Wigger, Delores S. Williams, Eugenia Williams, Lois Wilson, and Miriam Therese Winter.
Biographical Note
Dr. Sherry Jordon was awarded her Ph.D in Theology from Yale in 1995 and is currently Associate Professor of Theology at the University of St. Thomas. She specializes in historical theology, particularly the Reformation period, and Women's Studies. Jordon served on the Coordinating Council of the Re-Imagining Community from 1998-2003, spoke at the 2003 Re-Imagining Gathering, and wrote an essay on feminist theology for Bless Sophia: Worship, Liturgy, and Ritual of the Re-Imagining Community. As part of her current research on the history and theology of Re-Imagining, she completed sixty-five oral interviews with members of the Re-Imagining Community, leading feminist and womanist theologians who presented at the conferences, people who were on the national staff of the women's units in the Presbyterian (USA) and United Methodist churches, and authors who have written books related to Christian feminism and/or Re-Imagining.
Feminist theology; Re-Imagining Conference (1993: Minneapolis, Minn.); Ecumenical Decade of the Churches in Solidarity with Women (Program); Andrew, Elizabeth, 1969-; Bass, Diana Butler, 1959-; Bednarowski, Mary Farrell; Bettenhausen, Elizabeth; Bishop, Nadean; Black, Kathy, 1956-; Blackstock, Donna, 1942-; Blons, Steven; Brinkley, Robert; Brock, Rita Nakashima; Buchanan, John M., 1938-; Chinn, Nancy, 1940-; Christensen, Faye, 1944-; Chung, Hyun Kyung; Cole, Susan, 1945-; Craig, J. Ann; Craig, Susan Halcomb, 1941-; Deacon-Weber, Kathy, 1954-; DeSouza, Sister Holy Spirit; Elkins, Heather Murray; Evans, Sara M. (Sara Margaret), 1943-; Fithian, Marylee, 1936-; Gates, Mary, 1934-; Hallman, Marchelle; Hames, Susan, 1944-; Henry, Robin, 1952-; Hinderlie, Maren; Hobday, José; Hunt, Mary E., 1951-; Joern, Pamela Carter, 1948-; Johnson, Katie; Johnson, Sally Howell; Jordon, Sherry E. (Sherry Elaine); Keely, Barbara Anne, 1952-; Kersting, Betty, 1936-; Kim, Judith Allen, 1946-; King, Annie Wu, 1933-; Kiser, Rebecca Lynn, 1954-; Kuhns, Mary, 1945-; Kwok, Pui-lan; Lund, Barbara, 1964-; Lundblad, Barbara K., 1944-; Lundy, Mary Ann Weese, 1933-; Mahle, Katherine Austin, 1945-; Marlow, Eily, 1975-; Martin, Joan M. (Joan Marie); Medinger, Mary Kaye, 1946-; Mercer, Joyce Ann, 1957-; Mollenkott, Virginia R.; Morrison, Susan, 1943-; Moschella, Mary Clark; Nelsen, Vivian Jenkins; Nelson, Randy, 1941-; Niles, John, 1945-; Olson, Manley, 1936-; Pagelkopf, Doris, 1938-; Peters, Rebecca Todd; Pharr, Virginia; Powell, Joy Mincey; Preus, Mary; Primavesi, Anne, 1934-; Reagon, Bernice Johnson, 1942-; Ringgenberg, Jo; Sauter, Mary Kay; Slettom, Jeanyne B.; Smith, Jerie; Sohl, Joyce D.; Stokes, Allison, 1942-; Strausz-Clement, John; Strausz-Clement, Judith; Swanson, Sue; Taussig, Hal; Thomas, Margaret; Tollefson, Rebecca; Valenzuela, Carmen; Van Wijk-Bos, Johanna W. H., 1940-; Wigger, Emily; Williams, Delores S.; Williams, Eugenia; Winter, Miriam Therese; Spann, Hilda; Ortega, Ofelia; Morrison, Melanie, 1949-; Adams, Martha O.; Aldredge-Clanton, Jann, 1946-; Allan, Gail, 1954-; Neuger, Christine Cozad, 1952-; Wilson, Lois
- Oral History Interviews, 2015-2016
  Scope and Contents
  Series contains 70 oral history interviews conducted with participants in the Re-Imagining conferences, including the first gathering in 1993.
  Access to Audio and Transcripts
  Audio recordings and transcripts for most of the interviews in this series are available in the Duke Digital Repository - Reimagining Collection. For interviews where the "Play Audio" button does not appear below the interviewee name, transcripts have not been created -- these recordings may be requested by following the "Request for Onsite Use" button.
  - Adams, Martha O., 2018-04-03
    - Adams_Martha_1.mp3 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0002, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0002)
    - Adams_Martha_2.mp3 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0002, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0002)
  - Aldredge-Clanton, Jann, 2016-07-28
    - Aldredge-Clanton_Jann_finaledit.wav (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0002, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0002)
  - Allan, Gail, 2018-07-12
    - Allan_Gail_original.m4a (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0002, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0002)
  - Andrew, Elizabeth, 2016-03-09; 67
  - Bass, Diana Butler, 2016-06-25; 75
  - Bednarowski, Mary, 2016-02-08; 68
  - Bishop, Nadean, 2016-01-25; 69
  - Black, Kathleen, 2016-03-21; 70
  - Blackstock, Donna, 2016-05-24; 71
  - Brock, Rita, 2016-05-15; 73
  - Buchanan, John, 2016-04-12; 74
  - Chinn, Nancy, 2016-03-22; 76
  - Christensen, Faye, 2016-08-12; 77
  - Chung, Hyun Kyung, 2015-11-09; 78
  - Craig, Ann, 2016-04-22; 79
  - Craig, Susan, 2016-03-31; 80
  - Deacon-Weber, Kathy, 2016-01-25; 81
  - Elkins, Heather Murray, 2016-05-03; 82
  - Evans, Sara, 2016-02-09; 83
  - Fithian, Marylee, 2015-10-29; 84
  - Gates, Mary, 2016-03-07; 85
  - Hames, Susan, 2016-06-01; 86
  - Henry, Robin, 2016-07-26; 87
  - Hunt, Mary, 2016-04-06; 88
  - Keely, Barbara Anne, 2016-04-21; 89
  - Kersting, Betty, 2016-04-11; 90
  - Kim, Judith, 2016-04-05; 91
  - King, Annie Wu, 2016-05-24; 92
  - Kiser, Rebecca, 2016-06-24; 93
  - Kuhns, Mary, 2016-04-03; 94
  - Kwok, Pui Lan, 2015-11-16; 95
  - Lund, Barbara, 2016-07-26; 96
  - Lundblad, Barbara, 2015-10-28; 97
  - Lundy, Mary Ann, 2016-02-15; 98
  - Mahle, Katherine, 2016-02-18; 99
  - Marlow, Eily, 2016-04-20; 100
  - Martin, Joan, 2015-11-16; 101
  - Medinger, Mary Kaye, 2016-05-23; 102
  - Mercer, Joyce Ann, 2016-05-25; 103
  - Mollenkott, Virginia, 2016-03-16; 104
  - Morrison, Melanie S., 2017-05-17
  - Morrison, Susan, 2016-04-09; 105
  - Moschella, Mary, 2016-03-24; 106
  - Nelsen, Vivian, 2016-05-16; 107
  - Nelson, Randy, 2016-02-04; 108
  - Neuger, Christie, 2018-02-05
    - Neuger_Christie.mp3 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0002, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0002)
  - Niles, John, 2016-05-04; 109
  - Olson, Manley, 2016-01-13; 110
  - Ortega, Ofelia, 2017-06-23
  - Pagelkopf, Doris, 2016-05-02; 111
  - Peters, Rebecca Todd, 2016-04-24; 112
  - Preus, Mary, 2016-07-07; 113
  - Sacred Journey: Sally Howell Johnson, Steven Blons, Robert Brinkley, 2016-07-25; 114
  - Sauter, Mary Kay, 2016-02-12; 115
  - Slettom, Jeanyne, 2016-05-26; 116
  - Smith, Jerie, 2016-01-26; 117
  - Sohl, Joyce, 2016-04-22; 118
  - Spann, Hilda, 2017-04-04
  - Stokes, Allison, 2016-03-21; 119
  - Strausz-Clement, John, 2016-04-13; 120
  - Strausz-Clement, Judith, 2016-06-14; 121
  - Swanson, Sue, 2016-01-20; 122
  - Taussig, Hal and Cole, Susan Cady, 2015-11-13; 123
  - Thomas, Margaret, 2016-04-13; 125
  - Tollefson, Rebecca, 2016-04-15; 126
  - Van Wijk-Bos, Johanna, 2016-04-18; 72
  - Wigger, Emily, 2016-04-07; 127
  - Williams, Genie, 2016-02-10; 128
  - Wilson, Lois, 2018-03-17
    - Wilson_Lois.mp3 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0002, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0002)
  - Winter, M.T., 2016-06-08; 129
- Re-Imagining Conferences, 1993-2000
  - 1993 Rituals, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 1
    - Spirit of Re-Imagining, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 1
      - 1993_Ritual_1.mp3, 0:47:20 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1993_Ritual_2.mp3, 0:32:23 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1993_Ritual_3.mp3, 0:07:23 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1993_Ritual_4.mp3, 0:12:14 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Re-Imagining God, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 2
      - 1993_Ritual_5.mp3, 0:36:25 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1993_Ritual_6.mp3, 0:04:49 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1993_Ritual_7.mp3, 0:16:29 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Re-Imagining Jesus, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 3
      - 1993_Ritual_8.mp3, 0:08:43 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Re-Imagining Community, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 4
      - 1993_Ritual_9.mp3, 0:49:15 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1993_Ritual_10.mp3, 0:09:53 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1993_Ritual_11.mp3, 0:20:21 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Re-Imagining Language - Word, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 5
      - 1993_Ritual_12.mp3, 0:06:24 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Re-Imagining Ethics-Work-Ministry, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 6
      - 1993_Ritual_13.mp3, 0:06:39 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - The Ritual of Sunday, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 7
      - Ritual_14_1993_Ritual_of_Sunday_Part_A.mp3, 0:45:28 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Ritual_15_1993_Ritual_of_Sunday_Part_B.mp3, 0:47:04 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Ritual_16_1993_Ritual_of_Sunday_Part_C.mp3, 0:44:36 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Ritual_17_1993_Ritual_of_Sunday_Part_D.mp3, 0:37:08 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
  - 1993 Speakers, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 2
    - Spirit of Re-Imagining: Mary Bednarowski, Bernice Johnson Reagon, Hyun-Kyung Chung, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 8
      - 1_1993_Mary_Bednarowski.mp3, 0:22:52 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1993_Bernice_Johnson_Reagon.mp3, 0:26:56 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_1993_Hyun_Kyung_Chung_Talk_1.mp3, 0:27:09 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0001)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0002)
    - Re-Imagining God: Speakers: Hyun-Kyung Chung, Rita Nakishima Brock, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 9
      - 1_1993_Hyun-Kyung_Chung_Talk_2.mp3, 0:51:11 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1993_Rita_Nakishima_Brock.mp3, 0:42:56 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0003)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0004)
    - Re-Imagining Jesus: Delores Williams, Kwok Pui Lan, Barbara Lundblad, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 10
      - 1_1993_Delores_Williams.mp3, 0:42:05 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1993_Kwok_Pui_Lan.mp3, 0:32:24 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_1993_Barbara_Lundblad.mp3, 0:31:38 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1993_ReImagining_Jesus_Q&A.mp3, 0:23:07 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0005)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0006)
    - Re-Imagining Creation: Anne Primavesi, Sr. Jose Hobday, Elizabeth Bettenhousen, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 11
      - 1_1993_Anne_Primavesi.mp3, 0:38:01 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1993_Sr_Jose_Hobday.mp3, 0:36:48 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_Elizabeth_Bettenhausen.mp3, 0:31:10 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 4_1993_Q_and_A.mp3, 0:23:05 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0007)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0008)
    - Re-Imagining Church as Spiritual Institution: Ada Maria Isasi-Diaz, Joan martin, Violet Al Raheb, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 12
      - 1_Ada_Mar'ia_Isasi-Di'az.mp3, 0:36:34 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_Joan_Martin.mp3, 0:34:37 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_Violet_Al_Raheb.mp3, 0:36:17 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 4_ReImagining_Church_Q&A.mp3, 0:21:32 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0009)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0010)
    - Re-Imagining Women-Arts-Church: Nancy Chinn, Nalini Jayusuria, Ingeline Nielsen, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 13
      - 1_Nancy_Chinn.mp3, 0:35:42 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_Nalini_Jayusuria.mp3, 0:30:38 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_Ingeline_Nielsen.mp3, 0:37:14 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 4_RE-IMAGINING_Women-Arts-Church_Q&A.mp3, 0:16:40 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0011)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0012)
    - Re-Imagining Community: Lois Wilson, Mercy Oduyoye, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 14
      - 1_1993_Lois_Wilson.mp3, 0:50:44 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_Mercy_Amba_Oduyoye.mp3, 0:49:33 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0013)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0014)
    - Re-Imagining Language-Word: Johanna Bos, Rosario Battle, Jacqueline Grant, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 15
      - 1_1993_Johanna_Bos.mp3, 0:40:37 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1993_Rosario_Battle.mp3, 0:36:13 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_1993_Jacqueline_Grant.mp3, 0:36:14 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 4_ReImagining_Language-Word_Q&A.mp3, 0:09:16 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0015)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0016)
    - Re-Imagining Sexuality-Family: Frances Wood, Mary Hunt, Susan Thistlethwaite, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 16
      - 1_1993_Frances_Wood.mp3, 0:42:38 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1993_Mary_Hunt.mp3, 0:51:36 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_1993_Susan_Thistlethwaite.mp3, 0:26:36 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 4_ReImagining_Sexuality-Family_Q&A.mp3, 0:13:39 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0017)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0018)
    - Re-Imagining Ethics-Work-Ministry, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 17
      - 1_1993_Beverly_Harrison.mp3, 0:31:49 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1993_Aruna_Gnanadason.mp3, 0:35:04 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_1993_Shawn_Copeland.mp3, 0:24:06 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 4_ReImagining_Ethics-Work-Ministry_Q&A.mp3, 0:14:57 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0019)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0020)
    - Re-Imagining Church as Worshipping Community: Virginia Ramey Mollenkott, Christine Smith, Ofelia Ortega, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 18
      - 1_1993_Virginia_Ramey_Mollenkott.mp3, 0:41:41 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1993_Christine_Smith.mp3, 0:30:23 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 3_1993_Ofelia_Ortega.mp3, 0:44:23 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 4_ReImagining_Church_as_Worshipping_Q&A.mp3, 0:06:46 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0021)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0022)
    - Re-Imagining the Ritual of Sunday: Proclamation - Christine Smith, 1993-11-4/1993-11-7; 19
      - 1993_Christine_Smith.mp3, 0:45:47 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0023)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0024)
  - 1994 Rituals, 1994-10-29; 3
    - Ritual 1, 1994-10-29; 20
      - 1994_Ritual_1.mp3, 0:21:07 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Ritual 2, 1994-10-29; 21
      - 1994_Ritual_2.mp3, 0:12:38 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Ritual 3, 1994-10-29; 22
      - 1994_Ritual_3.mp3, 0:10:45 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Ritual 4, 1994-10-29; 23
      - 1994_Ritual_4.mp3, 0:22:31 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Ritual 5, 1994-10-29; 24
      - 1994_Ritual_5.mp3, 0:06:19 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Ritual 6, 1994-10-29; 25
      - 1994_Ritual_6_-_Ending_Ritual.mp3, 0:26:47 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
  - 1994 Speakers, 1994-10-29; 4
    - Theology Revisited, 1994-10-29; 26
      - 1_1994_Rita_Nakashima_Brock.mp3, 0:24:58 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1994_Theology_Revisited_Q&A_Virginia_PharrandRita_Brock.mp3, 0:33:36 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Imagining The Heart of God, 1994-10-29; 27
      - 1994_Pamela_Carter_Joern.mp3, 0:14:50 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Incarnation - Christ as the Heart of the Community, 1994-10-29; 28
      - 1_1994_Rita_Nakashima_Brock.mp3, 0:26:50 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1994_Incarnation_Q&A.mp3, 0:14:48 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
  - 1994 Community Development, 1994-10-29; 5
    - Community Development, 1994-10-29; 29
      - 1994_Community_Development_Birthgivers_and_Vision_Groups.mp3, 0:12:46 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Gathering_The_Word_and_Sounding_The_Word.mp3, 0:48:21 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Ritual_1.mp3, 0:33:24 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0025)
  - 1995 Gathering - Soundings: Re-Imagining the Word, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 6
    - Being the Word, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 30
      - 1995_Breaking_Open_Our_Words_Miriam_Therese_Winter.mp3, 0:28:08 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - Being the Word, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 31
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0026)
      - 1995_Ritual_2.mp3, 0:20:17 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0026)
    - Walking with Sophiaword, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 32
      - 1995_Ritual_3.mp3, 0:17:25 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0027)
    - Listening to Sophiaword, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 33
      - 1995_Announcements_Mary_Kay_Sauter.mp3, 0:08:33 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Ritual_4.mp3, 0:12:06 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Ritual_5.mp3, 0:07:08 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Unbinding_the_Word_Miriam_Therese_Winter_Part_A.mp3, 0:57:34 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)